Hello, my name is Mirei Suganami. This is Mirei Suganami and
Mirei Suganami and Saya Kanazaki of Natto Corelumi!
Today we are here at at-cosmetics!
It's amazing!
Yay!
Well, what do you know, today, Hanya and Hii-chan
Hanya and Hii-chan were doing a frame-buying project.
We are going to do the same thing!
I'm so happy!
Thank you so much!
I was kind of jealous of you, wasn't I?
I was so jealous!
The budget was 50,000 yen, 25,000 yen each.
Wow! Oh my God!
That's really bad!
Really, really, really! Let's buy what we really want!
Yes, I'll buy what I really want!
But we have only one hour to do so!
I'm going to look and buy quickly!
Yes, sir!
Okay, I'm off!
First, the ranking!
Oh, wow!
What? There's a protein that tastes so good!
I didn't know they sold protein.
I'm using this eyelash serum.
Hess, you guys have really long lashes, so...
I'm using the Dior concealer.
It's really running out!
Chance, chance, chance!
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. I'll monitor one.
Okay, you can keep an eye on it.
Wow, I don't know what to do.
Anyway, you know what?
I'm gonna run out of something I already have.
I'm gonna run out of, like, concealer or something.
I need some foundation, too, so...
I think I'm going to go look for a repeat purchase of something I already have.
I think I'm going to go look now.
Ta-da!
This is Shinigami-mura's foundation.
This one has already been on the Ikonoichi Channel.
when I introduced some of my daughters with Hin-chan.
I've already introduced it to you.
I don't know how many times I've used it.
I'm about to run out, so I'm going to buy it!
Which color?
I don't know.
The lightest color. Oh, I think it's No. 594.
Ta-da! The concealer I mentioned earlier.
Concealer and foundation!
6,600 yen. Oh, it's less than 20,000 yen. Oh, no, no, no, no!
What should I do?
Maya wants at least one more Depakos.
Which one? I want a lipstick from Yves Salloran.
I need a specific color. I used to use it.
I used to use it a long time ago, and it made me feel like a good woman.
It makes my lips feel soft and supple, and I don't get any cracks.
I'm in the market for a red lipstick right now.
I'd like to have a look at it.
Oh, but it's cute.
Oh!
It's so cute!
Oh, wait, it's so cute.
It really is.
It's so shiny.
Number six? This color.
It's super pretty. I love it.
This one's a little brownish.
Wait, they're both pretty.
It's pretty.
Yeah, they're a little different.
What? The same?
Same.
What?
It's the same color, Mr. Tespan.
I can't find it.
What's more...
It's a little different.
It's the same.
It's the same.I'm with you.
We're together.
Wait, maybe this is it.
Maybe it's fate.
I'll buy you my number 6 lip.
Yeah, you're right.
Number 6 is calling my name.
I'll buy it.
It's my number six lip of destiny.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Okay, Miyutto.
Spray? Spray, make-up keep. I want Cosme Decorte's make-up keep. Where is it?
Do you think they have it? I'm sure they have it.
Makeup Keep. Makeup Keep?
There it is! That's it! That's it! That's it!
Yes!
It's in! Oh, my God! You know, I think you guys see this a lot.
This is so good. This is so good. Here it is! This one's 3,000 yen.
Great! And, you know, I want to buy this one.
I want to buy this one. Wait, I want Saya too! Yeah! Eyeliner. My favorite eyeliner.
Ruin Makeup is so good! It's really good! Eyeliner at 5 o'clock live
Saya...
I'll use the brown one. I like the deep brown one.
I'll use this one.
Is there eyebrow mascara down there?
Do you have it?
Wow.
Wait a minute.
What is it?
You know what?
It's for the witch.
Yes! The witch...
You know, you were saying...
Oh! An eyelash beauty machine?
I'll buy one.
Oh! I love it.
Ta-da! My favorite.
It's great!
It's going to run out.
I put it in.
I love it.
Do you have any brow mascara?
What do you usually use?
I don't usually use brow mascara.
But I'm looking to brighten up my brows a little bit.
I'm just looking for something to brighten them up a little bit.
I don't know.
What time is it?
Is there any more time?
No, I don't.
Half an hour.
Oh, shit.
Got it.
You got it?
It's got a lot of power in it.
Electric.
It's a pinkish-ash hair color.
Here.
This is the pinkish ash.
Yeah. - Yeah.
And it's nice to have a tester.
Mm-hmm.
Ah!
That sounds like wisdom.
Really?
I don't know what to do.
But if I have to change the color in the future...
I don't know.
Let's go with pink.
What about this one?
Bring it back a little bit.
They're both pretty.
Yeah, they're both pretty.
Why don't you do it again?
Oh, no.
Let's be careful.Let's go carefully.
Let's go carefully.
OK, I bought it.
I got it.
Oh, wait.
I have some annul cereal sunscreen.
Japanese.
Sunscreen.
Anessa.
Wait, I want to buy some Ally.
I want to buy some Ally. I want to buy some Ally.
Who or what's the difference? What's the difference?
What's the difference?
Gel.
I guess this is the most standard one.
Sure, sure, sure.
I'm thinking
I think I'll go with gel.
Anessa again this year.
Oh...
I want this.
Let's get one.
ANDB
I'll buy it.
That's nice.
How many are you getting?
I'll buy one.
Eight hundred yen.
Oh, yeah!
That's 770 yen.
I'll buy two.
Oh, that's good!
No, thanks!
It's good, it's good.
What's this?
Oh, this.
It's in the electric packet.
What?
I don't know.
It's got protein in it or something.
I'm more interested in the food stuff.
Oh, collagen.
Do you want some collagen?
Yeah, I'll have some.
It's 810 yen.
That's right.
810 yen.
I'll buy some!
Collagen.
Cheers!
Let's go that way.
Okay, let's go.
Oh, wait, I want some purple shampoo.
Oh, wait, me too.
Oh, Somarka!
I love Somarka.
You dye it?
I like Somarka.
I'll buy it.
Buy it, buy it, buy it.
Somarka.
I'll get it.
Oh, wait, I want to buy a comb.
Let's buy a comb!
I'll buy a brush
Wait, what should I do? I don't know which one is good.
I want this kind of brush that makes my hair smooth and silky.
That's right.
Then I'll buy this one.
This one's good.
I don't know how much it costs.
Hold the little one.
Really?
I'll get you a towel for your hair.
Oh, wow, I didn't know they had them.
I'll get you one.
Jo Malone perfume. Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Oh, am I right? Jo Malone.
Jo Malone. Jorma.
I can't say it, I'm really with you. I've done this crap like 10 times.I can't tell you how many times I've been through this crap.
My friend gave me this hand cream for my birthday, and I've been wanting to buy some perfume.
I don't know which one is better. It's really hard.
I don't have time to worry about this.
Excuse me. Is that okay?
You're choosing.
Time.
Wait.
Oh, here it is, here it is, here it is!
Here, here, here!
Right this way!
I did it!
I could've gone on for like five minutes.
I only said it back to him for about five minutes.
You lost time.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
But that's great.
Yay! Yay!
Yay, yay, yay!
I'm a fan of Clarins oil.
I have so much of it.
And the packaging's changed.
Yeah, it's changed.
I wonder how much it costs.
I don't know anymore.
She's never going.
Let's put one last thing in there.
What are you putting in there?
Put something in it.
Let's get some toothpaste.
Toothpaste?
Oh, my God, it's important.
Oh, my God, it's electric.
Electric, please.
No, thank you.
Last minute shopping for toothpaste.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm going, Karin.
Yes, I'll go.
I'll go and buy all of them.
You can do it!
Yes, I'm fine. Great.
The total?
Wow!
If it's over 51,111 yen...
No, no, no, no.
I vote we definitely go over.
About 1,000 yen. I'm sorry, there's another bag included, so here's the total.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Then you're on your own.
Yes, that's right.
Price on your own.
Wow.
Yes, so I bought a lot... A lot of them. 50,000 yen view.
50,000 yen view, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle!
I'd like to introduce what I bought. I'll start first.
I bought these... First of all, these are my eyelash protectors.
First of all, I bought Majolica Majorca's eyelash serum, which has always protected my eyelashes.
I also bought a natural mix brush that makes my lashes look shiny.
I also bought some sunscreen from Ally, which is my natural enemy in the summer.
I also bought my favorite eyeliner, Jet Black, because it's the only black eyeliner I can use.
And I bought a black sponge and two win!
This is COSME DECORTE Comfort Ray Mist Set & Protect.
Makeup Keep Mist, this is Diorskin Forever Skin Correct Concealer.
I bought this concealer in the lightest color I could find.
Ingdishbear and Freesia cologne... it took me a long time to choose... but I'm going to take good care of it.
That's all!
And that's all.
Oh, yes, it's colorful.
Okay, next up, I'll introduce...
Cafonico Hair Dry Microfiber Towel Pink
Pink.
A hair towel designed by a hair stylist.
When you sleep with your hair, you really need to use a towel that is designed with your hair in mind.
If you don't use a towel that really considers the quality of your hair, it will be really damaged.
I'm really happy about this.
Anessa sunscreen
I'm an Anessa fan and you are an Ally fan, so I got this!
I got it!
Gel typeGel type
Easy to apply
Collagen Darink
This is very important, Collagen Darink, because it was displayed in a very big place, and it was ranked very high.
I'll try it and let you know how it goes.
And I bought it at the last minute.
And the toothpaste I bought at the last minute, I chose the one that wasn't minty!
And the eyebrow mascara!
Kisumi Heavy Rotation Coloring Eyebrow No. 10 in Pink Ash.
Now that I've lightened my hair, I'm going to use a brow mascara.
This is also a Kismi Heroine Makeup eyeliner, and Miretan bought the black one.
Seya bought the brown one, the deep brown one.
Brown eyeliner is my favorite color!
And the big one.
shuemura nandimited lusking fluid, total #4, the lightest color, map type.
My skin is not complete without it. I love it!
And this one, Somalkar's Color Shampoo Purple.
I'm going to try to get a good hair quality with this and this and this set.
And Clarins Lip Conefort Oil No. 02.
Miretan said this is really good!
It's really good!
I have other colors.
I have other colors, but this is the first time I'm using this purplish color, so I'm really looking forward to it!
And remember?
What was it?
Number 6. I bought it first.
So much has happened in an hour.
I might have forgotten it by now.
Rouge Volupte Candy Glaze No. 6 by Ibsa Nolan.
It's the number 6 lip of destiny.
That's two great lipsticks.
I'm so glad I bought so many!
And this...
I got it as a gift.
Souvenirs?
It's an essential treatment.
It says "treatment" on it.
He looks so happy!
So I bought a bunch of stuff!
Please visit at-cosmetics and see what they have to offer!
Let's review!
Bye bye!